White Man's Town... Black Man's Law!
Boss Nigger is a western, action, comedy film directed by Jack Arnold.
Two black bounty hunters ride into a small town
out West in pursuit of an outlaw.
They discover that the town has no sheriff, and soon take over that
position, much against the will of the mostly white townsfolk.
Boss Nigger, played by Fred Williamson.
Amos, played by D'Urville Martin.
Mayor Griffin, played by R.G. Armstrong.
Miss Pruitt, played by Barbara Leigh.
Jed Clayton, played by William Smith.
Boss Nigger (also known as Boss and The Black Bounty Killer) is a 1975 blaxploitation Western film directed by Jack
Arnold, starring former football player Fred Williamson, who also wrote and co-produced the film.
It is the first film for which Williamson was
credited as screenwriter or producer.
The tone is lighthearted.